Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
Is anybody there?
هل يوجد أحد هناك؟
Open the door quickly!
افتح الباب بسرعة!
Open up!
إفتح!
Yunniang!
يونيانغ!
Yunniang is missing!
يونيانغ مفقود!
Sister!
أخت!
I searched everywhere for Yunniang.
لقد بحثت في كل مكان عن يونيانغ.
Sister,
أخت،
but she was nowhere to be found.
ولكن لم يتم العثور عليها في أي مكان.
Until one day,
حتى يوم واحد،
I saw Scholar Yang on the street.
رأيت الباحث يانغ في الشارع.
Why are you here again?
لماذا أنت هنا مرة أخرى؟
Weren't you forbidden to come?
ألم يكن ممنوعا عليك الحضور؟
That's when I learned
وهنا تعلمت
that the normally well-dressed scholar
أن الباحث الذي يرتدي ملابس أنيقة عادة
was actually a gambling addict in private.
كان في الواقع مدمنًا للمقامرة على انفراد.
Yunniang's disappearance
اختفاء يونيانغ
must be connected to him.
يجب أن تكون متصلا به.
It didn't take long for me to figure out
لم يستغرق الأمر وقتًا طويلاً حتى أتمكن من اكتشاف ذلك
it was him.
لقد كان هو.
To get gambling money,
للحصول على أموال المقامرة،
he sold Yunniang to the gambling house owner.
باع يونيانغ إلى صاحب بيت القمار.
The gambling house owner, to bribe the county officials,
صاحب بيت القمار، لرشوة مسؤولي المقاطعة،
gave Yun Niang to Secretary Zhao.
أعطى يون نيانغ للسكرتير تشاو.
My poor sister
أختي المسكينة
survived only a few days under Secretary Zhao
نجا فقط بضعة أيام تحت قيادة السكرتير تشاو
before being tortured to death.
قبل أن يتعرض للتعذيب حتى الموت.
How could I swallow this anger?
كيف يمكنني أن أتغلب على هذا الغضب؟
They deserve to die.
إنهم يستحقون الموت.
But why use such means
ولكن لماذا نستخدم مثل هذه الوسائل
and sacrifice yourself too?
وتضحي بنفسك أيضًا؟
As long as I can avenge my sister,
طالما أستطيع الانتقام لأختي،
I don't care what happens to me.
لا يهمني ما يحدث لي.
This is the only keepsake my sister left me.
هذه هي الهدية الوحيدة التي تركتها لي أختي.
Sister.
أخت.
Niaoniao won't be with you anymore.
لن يكون نياونياو معك بعد الآن.
Don't be afraid.
لا تخف.
Kill her.
اقتليها
She's the real culprit.
إنها الجاني الحقيقي.
Innkeeper,
صاحب النزل،
what's wrong with her?
ما بها؟
Kill her!
اقتلوها!
She's the one to blame.
إنها المسؤولة.
Watch out!
احذر!
Innkeeper!
صاحب النزل!
Are you alright?
هل انت بخير؟
Yunniang is already gone.
لقد ذهب يونيانغ بالفعل.
It's time for you to let go.
لقد حان الوقت لتترك الأمر.
What an adorable little pig!
يا له من خنزير صغير رائع!
Look how tiny it is,
انظر كم هو صغير
and chubby,
وسمينة،
and so delightful!
وهي جميلة جداً!
It's a good omen.
إنها فأل حسن.
Why don't we keep it
لماذا لا نحتفظ به
and raise it at home?
وتربيته في المنزل؟
This girl is really in trouble.
هذه الفتاة في ورطة حقيقية.
She's quite pitiful.
إنها مثيرة للشفقة تماما.
Let's help her.
دعونا نساعدها.
Silly girl.
فتاة سخيفة.
You're still young.
أنت لا تزال شابا.
You'll have to get married when you grow up.
سيتوجب عليك الزواج عندما تكبر.
Sister.
أخت.
Boss,
رئيس،
you're back.
لقد عدت.
What?
ماذا؟
Did I disappoint you?
هل خيبت ظنك؟
Boss,
رئيس،
I was wrong.
لقد كنت مخطئا.
Who put you up to this?
من دفعك إلى هذا؟
How did you know?
كيف عرفت؟
As if your pig brain could come up with this.
وكأن دماغ الخنزير الخاص بك يمكن أن يأتي بهذا.
Go back and get some rest first.
ارجع واحصل على بعض الراحة أولاً.
Boss.
رئيس.
It's over.
انتهى.
The innkeeper wouldn't really let me die, would he?
صاحب النزل لن يسمح لي بالموت حقًا، أليس كذلك؟
Take a good rest.
خذ قسطاً جيداً من الراحة.
Wait.
انتظر.
Let me lean on you.
دعني أعتمد عليك.
Are you still feeling unwell?
هل لازلت تشعر بالتوعك؟
I'm tired.
أنا متعب.
This is Fengxin's favorite thing.
هذا هو الشيء المفضل لدى فينجشين.
Fengxin.
فنغشين.
Sister.
أخت.
Sister,
أخت،
where are you?
أين أنت؟
I'm so scared,
أنا خائفة جداً
Fengxin.
فنغشين.
Sister.
أخت.
What is this?
ما هذا؟
What have you prepared?
ماذا أعددت؟
Sister.
أخت.
This is so beautiful,
هذا جميل جدا
I love it so much.
انا احبه كثيرا.
Look, Sister.
أنظري يا أختي.
Fengxin.
فنغشين.
Fengxin,
فنغشين،
I can't find you anymore.
لم أتمكن من العثور عليك بعد الآن.
Fengxin.
فنغشين.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
Sister.
أخت.
Sister,
أخت،
I have never blamed you.
لم ألومك أبدًا.
You need to be well
يجب أن تكون بخير
and live on.
والعيش على ذلك.
I'm sorry,
أنا آسف،
it's my fault for not protecting you.
إنه خطئي لأنني لم أحميك.
You're awake.
أنت مستيقظ.
Are you feeling better?
هل تشعر بتحسن؟
I'm hungry.
أنا جائع.
Why are you wrapping so slowly?
لماذا تقوم بالتغليف ببطء شديد؟
You do it then.
افعلها إذن.
It's delicious.
إنه لذيذ.
Aren't you eating?
ألا تأكل؟
Why are you grinning at me like that?
لماذا تبتسم لي هكذا؟
Boss.
رئيس.
You're actually being understanding of others now.
أنت في الواقع تتفهم الآخرين الآن.
I'm not holding a grudge against Zhu Niaoniao.
أنا لا أحمل ضغينة ضد تشو نيونياو.
It's because I know she was being used
هذا لأنني أعلم أنها كانت تستخدم
and is not the real culprit.
وليس هو الجاني الحقيقي.
Then who's behind her?
إذن من الذي خلفها؟
Dugu Qiongqi.
دوجو تشيونجكي.
The one from a thousand years ago
الذي يعود تاريخه إلى ألف عام
who turned us against each other.
الذين حولونا ضد بعضنا البعض.
What are you thinking about?
ماذا تفكر فيه؟
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
I'll take care of everything.
سأعتني بكل شيء.
Let's eat now.
دعونا نأكل الآن.
Qin Qi
تشين تشي
Dugu Qiongqi
دوجو تشيونجكي
Dongfang
دونغفانغ
What brings you here?
ما الذي أتى بك إلى هنا؟
We've been friends for so many years.
لقد كنا أصدقاء لسنوات عديدة.
Just came to see you.
لقد جئت فقط لرؤيتك.
Do I need an appointment?
أحتاج موعد؟
At least you still have a conscience.
على الأقل لا يزال لديك ضمير.
Have a seat.
خذ مقعدا.
What would you like to drink?
ماذا تحب أن تشرب؟
You've been quite busy lately, haven't you?
لقد كنت مشغولاً جدًا في الآونة الأخيرة، أليس كذلك؟
I have been rather busy,
لقد كنت مشغولاً إلى حد ما،
but since you're here, I'll make sure to treat you well.
لكن بما أنك هنا، سأتأكد من معاملتك بشكل جيد.
Busy using Zhu Niaoniao?
هل أنت مشغول باستخدام Zhu Niaoniao؟
Dugu Qiongqi.
دوجو تشيونجكي.
What did you say?
ماذا قلت؟
Am I wrong?
هل انا مخطئ؟
What should I call you then?
ماذا يجب أن أسميك إذن؟
Qin Qi?
تشين تشى؟
Or Dugu Qiongqi?
أو دوجو تشيونجكي؟
Did you remember something?
هل تذكرت شيئا؟
Underestimating your enemy leads to disaster.
إن التقليل من شأن عدوك يؤدي إلى الكارثة.
It won't happen again.
لن يحدث هذا مرة أخرى.
What are you talking about?
ماذا تتحدث عنه؟
You really don't remember me?
هل حقا لا تتذكرني؟
You're the one in black who's been causing trouble, aren't you?
أنت الشخص الذي يرتدي الأسود والذي يسبب المشاكل، أليس كذلك؟
What exactly do you want?
ماذا تريد بالضبط؟
So many years have passed.
لقد مرت سنوات عديدة.
How do you have one too?
كيف لديك واحدة أيضاً؟
This is the Huangquan Pendant.
هذه هي قلادة هوانغكوان.
In other words,
بعبارة أخرى،
it is us.
إنه نحن.
So you don't need to hate me.
لذلك لا داعي لأن تكرهني.
You think I would believe you?
هل تعتقد أنني سأصدقك؟
There's only this much work every day.
لا يوجد سوى هذا القدر من العمل كل يوم.
Why should I do more work
لماذا يجب علي أن أعمل أكثر؟
while you just sit here?
بينما أنت فقط تجلس هنا؟
You don't do anything.
أنت لا تفعل شيئا.
I won't do it.
لن افعل ذلك
Why should I?
لماذا يجب علي ذلك؟
You're already so fat.
أنت سمينة بالفعل.
What's wrong with doing some work?
ما الخطأ في القيام ببعض العمل؟
Who's fat?
من هو السمين؟
You are.
أنت.
Only you are fat.
أنت فقط سمين.
You're fat.
أنت سمين.
You're definitely fat.
أنت سمين بالتأكيد.
Boss.
رئيس.
Why are you dressed like a celebrity today?
لماذا ترتدي ملابس المشاهير اليوم؟
The flatterer was right.
وكان المتملق على حق.
But if I wore this outfit,
ولكن إذا ارتديت هذا الزي،
I'd look as beautiful as a goddess.
سأبدو جميلة كالإلهة.
Give me a break.
أعطني استراحة.
How annoying.
كم هو مزعج.
Where is Dongfang Zhaobai?
أين هو دونغفانغ تشاوباي؟
Sir.
سيد.
Mr. Dongfang left early this morning.
غادر السيد دونغفانغ في وقت مبكر من هذا الصباح.
He left?
هل غادر؟
Why didn't he tell me?
لماذا لم يخبرني؟
What are you thinking?
ماذا تفكر؟
It couldn't be...
لا يمكن أن يكون...